

Noah Chiu

Back-end Deputy Manager

Contact



0955-825-890



fg5678910@gmail.com



Tucheng District, New Taipei City

₩ Skills

- Go Language
- Python
- PostgreSQL
- Data Analysis
- JavaScript
- Problem Solving
- Software Design

Education

Bachelor of Electro-Optical Engineering National Taipei University of Technology

2017 - 2021

- Optics (ray/wave/electromagnetic)
- Calculus
- Algorithm(from Computer Science Engineering)
- Programming (C, Python)

Experience

Back-End Deputy Manager Smart Automation Technology Inc.

2023 - 2024

Managed task assignment and project timelines, ensuring efficient scheduling for subordinates. Planned and optimized database integrations. Conducted code reviews and logic optimization within the department.

Full-Stack Engineer Smart Automation Technology Inc.

2021 - 2023

Developed web systems (HRM, MES, WMS, QMS, PMS, OMS) and dashboards for production, efficiency, and yield. Proficient in Go, PostgreSQL, Python, ReactJS, integrated MySQL and Oracle databases into PostgreSQL, ensuring seamless data migration and compatibility across systems, and integrated APIs (REST, SOAP, RFC), Deployed systems using Linux, Docker, Nginx.

Management Information System Intern Everlight Electronics

2021- 2021

Designed company system architecture and managed internal cybersecurity. Assisted in maintaining security protocols. Handled emergency issues with personnel workstations.

Lego Robot EV3 Teacher Assistant IdeaROBO

2020-2020

Taught students EV3 programming and fostered their logical thinking skills. Trained them to approach challenges independently. Developed problem-solving abilities through hands-on learning.

About Me

Performance-driven Back-end Deputy Manager with a passion for learning, problem-solving, and delivering customized system solutions. Recognized for balancing independent tasks with effective collaboration in diverse environments, leading to successful project outcomes. I specialize in the development and maintenance of enterprise systems such as ERP, MES, WMS, and QMS. With a strong foundation in Go, Python, PostgreSQL, and front-end experience with JavaScript and ReactJS, focused on understanding customer needs to drive satisfaction and loyalty, enhancing the company's success. A fast learner who embraces new technologies and methodologies, I continuously enhance my skills through self-learning, language acquisition, and coding challenges, ultimately benefiting both the company and my personal growth.